lalibcosupport.com 2011-06-05

# Lalibcosupport.com

Lalibco.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We take appropriate security measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized access, unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. 

» Lalibco.com hereby declares, that we **never** sell or rent the personal details provided on our websites to any third party or unauthorized person. We use the latest and most sophisticated security techniques to protect our members’ private information.  
Lalibco.com uses self-developed privacy protection programs to make sure that your personal details are always kept confidential. 

» Every transaction in our system is processed in a **secure environment** and the provided details are posted to the authorized recipients via **encrypted** channels. Note that http://www.lalibcosupport.com/ uses similar security features to safeguard all the information posted on the website. 

» We will **never** send you any spam or promotional messages/e-mails. The provided details will **not** be used for promotional purposes. In accordance with all applicable laws and regulations, Lalib Lda. will send you automated e-mails to report the status of your transaction(s) made on any of our websites. 

» To ensure the protection of your credit card details, we **never** store them on our servers, thus making it impossible for hackers to obtain them. 

» We will **never** ask for your password. Please do not give out your login details to anyone who might compromise your membership. 

» Lalib Lda. may collect limited non-personally identifying information that your browser makes available whenever you submit one of our online forms. This information we collect may include your Internet IP address, the time and date and your browser configuration. This feature has been introduced to help identifying our customers, which may speed up the response time of our Customer Service department. 

» Please **never** send your credit card number to Lalibco.com. It is not safe to send this type of sensitive information to anyone via e-mail. 

Changes of the Privacy Policy

To guarantee perfect protection and satisfaction to our members, occasionally we need to update our Privacy Statement, reflecting the changes in our services. Changes of the Policy will be indicated at the top of the page showing the date of the last update. 

In case material changes are enacted, the update will appear on the website prominently to implementing the change. 

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us.
